 For Class I &amp; II Student Name - GR.NO.- Class - Roll No. Year- 2026-27 Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 25M CT-2 25M Term-1 100M CT- 3 25M CT- 4 25M Term- 2 100M 50% Term-1 50% Term-2 Final Result English -1 English -2 Hindi Gujarati Maths ENV Total Percentage Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 SUPW PT Karate Dance Discipline Cleanliness Attendance Total Attendance Co- Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 GK Computer Handwriting Spelling SLS Art &amp; Craft Teacher Remarks 83489 65902 Class Teacher Principal For Class I II to V Student Name - GR.NO.- Class - Roll No. Year- 2026-27 Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 25M CT-2 25M Term-1 100M CT-3 25M CT-4 25M Term-2 100M 50% Term-1 50% Term-2 Final Result English -1 English -2 Hindi Gujarati Maths Science Social Studies Total Percentage Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 SUPW PT Karate Dance Discipline Cleanliness Attendance Total Attendance Co- Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 GK Computer Handwriting Spelling SLS Art &amp; Craft Teacher Remarks 83489 65902 Class Teacher Principal For Class VI to VIII Student Name - GR.NO.- Class - Roll No. Year- 2026-27 Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 25M CT-2 25M Term-1 100M CT-3 25M CT-4 25M Term-2 100M 50% Term-1 50% Term-2 Final Result English -1 English -2 Hindi Gujarati Maths Physics Chemistry Biology Geography History&amp; Civics Total Percentage Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 Karate Dance Discipline Cleanliness Attendance Total Attendance Co- Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 GK Computer SLS Art &amp; Craft SUPW PT Teacher Remarks 83489 65902 Class Teacher Principal For Class IX Student Name - GR.NO.- Class - Roll No. Year- 2026-27 Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 25M CT-2 25M Term-1 80 M CT-3 25M CT-4 25M Term-2 80 M 50% Term-1 50% Term-2 Final Result English -1 English -2 Sec ond Language Third Language Maths Physics Chemistry Biology Geography History&amp; Civics Economic Application Total Percentage Co- Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 SLS Art &amp; Craft SUPW PT Karate Dance Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 Discipline Cleanliness Attendance Total Attendance Teacher Remarks 83489 65902 Class Teacher Principal For Class XI Student Name - GR.NO.- Class - Roll No. Year- 2026-27 Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 50 M CT-2 50 M Term-1 Marks Obtained CT-3 50 M CT-4 50 M Term- 2 ( Final Exam) Marks Obtained English -1 80 80 English -2 80 80 Maths 80 80 Physics 70 70 Chemistry 70 70 Biology 70 70 Physical Education 70 70 Total Percentage Co- Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 SUPW PT Discipline Cleanliness Attendance Total Attendance Teacher Remarks 83489 65902 Class Teacher Principal For Class XI I Student Name - GR.NO.- Class - Roll No. Year- 2026-27 Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term - 1 CT-3 CT-4 Pre-board Exam English -1 80 English -2 80 Maths 80 Physics 70 Chemistry 70 Biology 70 Physical Education 70 Total Percentage Co- Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 SUPW PT Discipline Cleanliness Attendance Total Attendance Teacher Remarks 83489 65902 Class Teacher Principal For Class X Student Name - GR.NO.- Class - Roll No. Year- 2026-27 Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 25M CT-2 25M Term-1 80M CT-3 25M CT-4 25M Pre board Exam 80M English -1 English -2 Sec ond Language Third Language Maths Physics Chemistry Biology Geography History&amp; Civics Economic Application Total Percentage Co- Scholastic Performance Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 SLS SUPW PT Subject CT-1 CT-2 Term-1 CT-3 CT-4 Term-2 Discipline Cleanliness Attendance Total Attendance Teacher Remarks 83489 65902 Class Teacher Principal 
